theimproper.com 2012-05-05

# Privacy : News, Gossip & Opinion on Pop Culture, Arts, Music, Theater, Film, Fashion, Dining, Celebrities « TheImproper.com

Please read this statement carefully before accessing and using TheImproper.com. Your use of TheImproper.com indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

 **Information Collection**

TheImproper.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. The Improper Online may collect information from users at several different points, but at all times this information will be kept confidential.

 **Comments**

Users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. Commenters may register anonymously. However, if a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Service we reserve the right to remove such comment. If we are required to by law to disclose commenters contact information, we will take all appropriate steps to protect the users identity.

 **Mailing List**

The Improper Online reserves the right to create and launch a mailing list. Users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests to qualify for inclusion. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list may receive regular emails from the site. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

 **Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, The Improper Online reserves the right to disclose personal information when required by law to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the GM Sites.

 **Business Transitions**

In the event The Improper Online goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

 **Links**

This site contain links to other sites. Please be aware that The Improper Online is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to read privacy statements where ever they are presented. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected The Improper Online.

 **Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to us by outside parties. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

 **Third Party Cookies**

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). The Improper Online has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by The Improper Online only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You have the right to opt out of this by clicking the following link and following the directions on that site. Yes I would like to [OPT OUT](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of third party cookies. [Opt Out by Clicking Here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

 **Notification of Changes**

All changes to this privacy statement, will be posted here and other places we deem appropriate to give our users ample opportunity to keep abreast of information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

 **Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact the editor at: editor@theimproper.com.

 **DMCA Compliance  
**  
TheImproper is fully compliant with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. If material is posted on this site on which you believe you hold a copyright, please contact us immediately and accept our assurance and our apologies that the material was posted in error and without knowledge of the said copyright and will be removed immediately upon notification in accordance with Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(1) also known as the Safe Harbor provision of the Act. Contact: Keith Girard at kgirard@theimproper.com, or by calling 646-246-4477, if you any questions or claims regarding this notice.

  * [](http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Privacy%20-%20http%3A%2F%2Fwww.theimproper.com%2Fprivacy%20\(via%20@sociablesite\) "Twitter")
  *
